

- SKILLS

HTML CSS - SCSS Bootstrap Git

React / Redux TypeScript Material UI

JavaScript GraphQL Node js Express

Postgres MongoDB

MUZAFFARBEK ABDUSAMATOV

Front-end Developer

- ABOUT ME

Hello. My name is Muzaffarbek.

I am full stack web developer with around 6 month of experience.

My role is to write and style the frontend components that meet the requirements of our mocks and fulfill our user stories.

Almost I professionally use HTML5, React / Redux, JavaScript , GRAPHQL, CSS / SASS, Node js, Express js, EJS...

Speak languages:

Uzbek English Russian

- CONTACT

+998 99 458 33 68 genrofer@gmail.com www.genrofer.ga Tashkent Uzbekistan

- EDUCATION HISTORY

Udemy

Online Courses Jan 2017 - July 2019

Najot Ta'lim

Education Centre in Tashkent Aug 2021 - May 2022

- WORK EXPERIENCE

Front end Developer

XXI asr buxgaltery May 2019 - Sep 2019

English teacher

English teacher Feb 2020 - Jun 2020

Full Stack Developer

Yosh Tadbirkor Sep 2021 - Feb 2022